chromecleanerpro.com 2018-12-16

# Privacy Policy | Chrome Cleaner Pro

By using this website you consent to this privacy policy. 

## What Information Do We Collect?

We may collect information from you when you fill out a form, when ordering or registering on our website, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address. Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional. 

Like most websites, we may use cookies, local storage or other similar technologies that are necessary to the proper functioning of our web site, related applications, tools and services, to enhance your experience and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'Do we use Local Storage and Cookies?' section below for information about cookies, local storage and how we use them. 

## What Do We Use Your Information For?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used to personalize your experience. Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs and improve this website, related apps and services. We continually work to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you. 

## Do We Use Local Storage and Cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small pieces of data that a site or its service provider can store locally on your own device through your Web browser, if you allow. You can learn more about cookies here.   
Also, we may collect and store information using HTML5 local storage and application data caches. We can use local storage to compile aggregate data about site traffic, site and apps interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and apps in the future.   
We do not store any personally identifiable information. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads and measure how users interact with website content on our site. You can control the ads you see and/or opt out of interest-based ads. Learn more about advertising cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy and terms. 

## Third Party Links

We do not distribute your personal information to third parties without your consent. 

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

## Do We Disclose Any Information to Third Parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to third parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. 

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

## Contact Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us by email at [info@chromecleanerpro.com](mailto:info@chromecleanerpro.com). 

Axel Division LP
